Colloquial Tamil by R.E. Asher and E. Annamalai.
Copyright R.E. Asher and E. Annamalai.
Recording copyright Routledge Limited 2002.
Welcome to Colloquial Tamil.
This recording begins with a section on pronunciation based on the section on pronunciation in the introduction to the accompanying book.
This part focuses on those Tamil sounds to which the beginner needs to pay particular attention, generally because they are unfamiliar to most speakers of English.
These pronunciation points are reinforced from time to time in later parts of the recording.
The recording continues with all the dialogues and other texts in the book.
There are also exercises from the book, along with some additional exercises for practice in listening comprehension and in speaking.
Where the tape contains material which is taken unchanged from the book, you may well listen to it with the book open in front of you.
However, you should also make a habit of listening without the help of the written text in order to increase your understanding of the spoken form.
When you are specifically asked to repeat a word or phrase, there is a short pause on the tape.
But you should use the pause button to repeat other phrases and longer utterances in order to give yourself lots of practice in speaking and understanding.